

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

I am a registered graduate Mechatronic Engineer with experience in industrial automation, mechatronic systems and web development with rapidly increasing range of industry experience and a proven record of procedural compliance.

Technical trainer with experience in teaching electrical engineering, mechatronics, industrial automation and robotics.

CORE QUALIFICATIONS

- Installation of mechanical components and machinery
- Product design and simulation
- Printed circuit boards design and fabrication
- Programming and Scripting of systems
- Fault diagnosis
- 3d Design and prototyping
- IOT designs and fabrication
- Skill on developing, implementing and evaluation of curriculum
- Teaching, assessing and class management skills
- Curriculum development

CERTIFICATIONS

- · Registered Graduate Engineer
- Certified Technical Trainer

REFEREES

Head of Mechatronics Engineering department, Dedan Kimathi University of Technology, 0113 969223

Mr. Collins Wahome Engineer, Software group, 0795321668

PAUL NDUNGU WAWERU

+254 741051915

wpaulndungu53@gmail.com

¶
10100, central, Kenya

EXPERIENCE

02/2020 - Current

TVET Technical Trainer Mathenge Technical Training Institute | Nyeri, Kenya

- My duties are to prepare lesson plan and teach students to help them acquire new skills
- Developed and distributed instructional materials to learners, assisting students with content mastery and retention.
- Equipped learners with practical skills and knowledge by arranging and coordinating workshops, demonstrations and conferences.

01/2018 - 12/2019

Graduate Trainee Dedan Kimathi University of Technology | Nyeri, Kenya

- As a graduate trainee I assisted in research and practical sessions under senior lecturer
- Trained and Worked on Siemens Mechatronic Systems, process automation and Analytics
- Researched and designed automated weather station using artificial intelligence.

02/2016 - 12/2017

Engineering Trainee CMC Motors | Nairobi, Kenya

- I Worked on motor vehicle fault diagnosis using off-board machine
- Dealt with Motor vehicle servicing, inspection and motor vehicle engine assembly.
- Completed daily list of assignments, contributing to engineer team by handling basic tasks and learning new skills.
- Maintained logbook over duration of training period, recording projects undertaken and skills learned.

EDUCATION

2023

Dedan Kimathi University of Technology

MSc: Advanced Manufacturing and Automation Engineering

2016

Dedan Kimathi University of Technology | DeKUT

B.Sc: Mechatronic Engineering

Acquired second class honours, upper division.

2022

Kenya School of TVET (KSTVET)

Higher National Diploma: Diploma in technical trainer education (Mechatronics) Acquired second class honours, upper division.

2010

Njumbi High School

Kenya Certificate of Secondary Education (KCSE) Attained an A minus